(Amy:)I'm going to the vending
machine. Do you want anything?
(Sheldon:)This is a simulation.
We have to survive
(Sheldon:)on the supplies we brought.
(Amy:)Okay, just checking.
(Raj:)We should have asked her
to get some Funyuns.
(Sheldon:)You're not going to have Funyuns
(Sheldon:)when we're a mile
below the surface of the Earth.
(Raj:)What if we brought them down
with us?
(Sheldon:)We'll take some Funyuns.
(Amy:)Anything else?
(Sheldon:)Some York Peppermint Patties,
(Penny:)a couple
of Dr. Peppers, and...
(Sheldon:)run to Best Buy and see if
they have a portable DVD player
(Sheldon:)and season one of a show
called Hannah Montana.
(Rajj:)Have her get season two.
(Sheldon:)Season one,
it was still finding itself.
(Bernadette:)Sorry you guys
had to see that.
Oh,
(Penny:)don't apologize.
Yeah.
(Leonard:)It just makes it a lot harder
to pretend it never happened.
(Bernadette:)Money's a sensitive subject
for Howie
(Bernadette:)because of the difference
in our income.
(Penny:)It really bothers him?
(Bernadette:)Well, sure.
There's still a lot of pressure
(Bernadette:)on guys to be providers.